<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ShopApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_new_account_sign_up"><font color="#040415">Create New Account? </font> <font color="#FC6828">Sign Up </font> </string>
    <string name="already_account_sign_in"><font color="#040415">Already have Account ? </font> <font color="#FC6828">Sign In </font> </string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="email"><font color="#040415">Email</font><font color="#FF0000">*</font> </string>
    <string name="backToLogin"><font color="#040415">Back to</font><font color="#FC6828"> Login</font> </string>
    <string name="policyandprivacy"> 1. Information We Collect

\nWe may collect the following types of information:

\nPersonal Information: We may collect personal information, such as your name, email address, shipping address, and payment information when you make a purchase.

\nDevice Information: We may collect information about the device you use to access our app, including the device type, operating system, and unique device identifiers.

\nUsage Information: We may collect information about how you use our app, including the pages you visit, the products you view, and the actions you take.

\n2. How We Use Your Information

\nWe use your information for the following purposes:

\nTo process and fulfill your orders.
\nTo communicate with you about your orders, promotions, and updates.
\nTo improve and personalize your experience with our app.
\To analyze and understand how users interact with our app.
\n3. Information Sharing

\nWe may share your information with:

\nService providers who help us with order processing, shipping, and other business functions.
\nLegal authorities if required by law or to protect our rights.
\n4. Your Choices

\nYou can:

\Update your account information.
\Opt-out of promotional emails.
\n5. Security

We take reasonable measures to protect your information from unauthorized access.

\n6. Changes to This Privacy Policy

\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review it periodically for changes.

\n7. Contact Us

\nIf you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at rubabahajiyeva@gmail.com.</string>
</resources>